Whoa! Whoa! [trembles]
What's happening to you?!
My Spirit of Hearth's Warming Presents
sense is going off!
That means a song is coming on!
Take a look at everything around you
All the smells that surely will astound you
Open up your heart, it will surround you
In the magic of Hearth's Warming Eve
The little things that make it better
Little ponies spreading cheer
Give a toy, a hug, a sweater
Memories that last all year
The present's always filled with presents
Large, medium, and small
Sometimes the most important things
Aren't very big at all
[tap-dancing solo]
What a party, there's so much to see here
Can't believe you didn't want to be here
You'd have had a blast, I guarantee here
This is the spirit of Hearth's Warming Eve
Cider's flowing, this is living
Come on and feel the beat
Life is better when you're giving
Each time you do it feels so sweet
The present's always filled with presents
So come on, open your eyes
Spend time with ponies just like you
And watch your spirits rise
The present's always filled with presents
Take a look around
The reason for the holiday
Is quite easily found
Yes, the reason for the holiday
And the reason is to be with your friends!